[Student] Okay. Wait, this has been so helpful. It's just like, it's so nice to see that someone else has gone over it and like actually thinks it's good.
[Avigail] Yeah, absolutely. Good work with everything. You've done a great job.
[Student] Yeah, I think I'm good. I feel much better that I have like ideas now, like solid ideas.
[Avigail] Yeah, absolutely. You're doing well.
[Student] Thank you.
Yeah, this was really helpful. Thank you so much.
[Avigail] Yeah, that's great to hear.
[Student] Thank you so much, by the way, because I feel like I wouldn't have executed this essay like so well without you.
Like, I'm so bad at executing my ideas. And like, I'm so like, I'm really happy with how it turned out.
Thank you so much.